//First create the STORE for questions and answers

const STORE = [
    { // Q 1
      question: "What was the first car EVER made by BMW?",
      answers: [
          'Motor-wagon',
          'Sport-Phaeton',
          'The Dixi',
          'Cybertruck'
      ],
      correctAns: 'The Dixi',
      image: 'https://media.giphy.com/media/Ph0oIVQeuvh0k/giphy.gif',
      imageAlt: 'Error'
    },

    { // Q 2
        question: 'When was BMW founded?',
        answers: [
            '1969',
            '1944',
            '1916',
            '1924'
        ],
        correctAns: '1916',
        image: 'https://media.giphy.com/media/12p16fWCjXIju0/giphy.gif',
        imageAlt: 'Error'
    },

    { // Q 3
        question: 'BMW also owns:',
        answers: [
            'Mercedez',
            'McLaren',
            'Rolls-Royce',
            'Ferrari'
        ],
        correctAns: 'Rolls-Royce',
        image: 'https://media.giphy.com/media/80bqJBvf3AGVq/giphy.gif',
        imageAlt: 'Error Screen'
    },

    { // Q 4
        question: 'The Headquarters in Munich, Bavaria is designed like: ',
        answers: [
            'a BMW Four-Cylinder Engine',
            'a BMW Six-Cylinder Engine',
            'a BMW V6 engine',
            'a BMW V8 engine'
        ],
        correctAns: 'a BMW Four-Cylinder Engine',
        image: 'https://media.giphy.com/media/HhgKxrRAsFqVi/giphy.gif',
        imageAlt: 'Error'
    },

    { // Q 5
        question: 'BMW built a: ',
        answers: [
            'Aston Martin',
            'Ferrari',
            'Lamborghini',
            '911'
        ],
        correctAns: 'Lamborghini',
        image:
        'https://media.giphy.com/media/628ghYe9EtEusohhxA/giphy.gif',
        imageAlt: 'Error'
    },

    { // Q 6
        question: "BMW built the WORLD'S fastest: ",
        answers: [
            'Supercar',
            'Motorbike',
            'Electric car',
            'Plane'
        ],
        correctAns: 'Motorbike',
        image: 'https://media.giphy.com/media/JGxy3K45MXXLG/giphy.gif',
        imageAlt: 'Error'
    },

    { // Q 7
        question: 'BMW was at the Forefront of:',
        answers: [
            'Engine Design',
            'Interior Design',
            'Aerodynamics Design',
            'Safety Design'
        ],
        correctAns: 'Aerodynamics Design',
        image: 'https://media.giphy.com/media/Y8a0CT2xsbo9G/giphy.gif',
        imageAlt: 'Error Screen'
    },

    { // Q 8
        question: 'BMW has been involved in:',
        answers: [
            'Go-kart Racing',
            'Motorcycle Racing',
            'Airplace Racing ',
            'Boat Racing'
        ],
        correctAns: 'Motorcycle Racing',
        image: 'https://media.giphy.com/media/3ZThmzHGe8dhe/giphy.gif',
        imageAlt: 'Error'
    },

    { // Q 9
        question: 'BMW won a Formula One Championship with:',
        answers: [
            '20-year-old street engine',
            '10-year-old street engine ',
            '5-year-old street engine ',
            '15-year-old street engine '
        ],
        correctAns: '20-year-old street engine',
        image: 'https://media.giphy.com/media/swTo29o1EtqDK/giphy.gif',
        imageAlt: 'Error'
    },

    { // Q 10
        question: 'The Signature Grille is Called',
        answers: [
            'Kidney Grille',
            'BMW Grille',
            'Grill',
            'Gloss Grille'
        ],
        correctAns: 'Kidney Grille',
        image: 'https://media.giphy.com/media/H6Sbf51oTwVEY/giphy.gif',
        imageAlt: 'Error'
    }
]
